<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Youngbeen&#39;s Resume</title>
      <link>/2022/03/07/youngbeen-s-resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/03/07/youngbeen-s-resume/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionMy name is Youngbeen Oh, I am currently studying Information Management at the University of Illinois at Urbana Champaign and am interested in data analytics and web application development.
I studied MIS which is Management Information Systems for my bachelor’s degree. So I had experience with SQL, database server and web application stuffs like HTML and CSS. And also, a little bit of project experience with R Studio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IS 407 Lab 01 Team Project</title>
      <link>/2022/02/15/is-407-hw-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/02/15/is-407-hw-02/</guid>
      <description>Lab1 - Nobel laureatesIn January 2017, Buzzfeed published an article on why Nobel laureates show immigration is so important for American science.You can read the article here.In the article they show that while most living Nobel laureates in the sciences are based in the US, many of them were born in other countries.This is one reason why scientific leaders say that immigration is vital for progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IS 407 HW 01</title>
      <link>/2022/02/01/is-407-hw-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/02/01/is-407-hw-01/</guid>
      <description>This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
HW 01 - Global plastic wastePlastic pollution is a major and growing problem, negatively affecting oceans and wildlife health.Our World in Data has a lot of great data at various levels including globally, per country, and over time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
